This is how I turn my feet into walking trampolines.
First, I do isometric holds at the start of my workout.
This helped push my vertical over 40 inches, but out of all the training I've ever done,
these are the simplest and most effective exercises.
It only takes 3 minutes.
First, get into a split position with your heel elevated.
Hold this for 30 seconds.
Studies have shown this little heel elevation to be more effective for ankle stiffness and
stability in the knee.
I do 3 sets of 30 seconds each side.
The next movement is almost the exact same thing.
We're still keeping the heel elevated, but now while doing short hops because it's important
to feel that elasticity in your tendons.
Do this for 3 sets of 12 each side.
And since the only goal is stiffer ankles, you can do this anywhere using just about
anything you have available.
Make sure you're still doing strength movements to support your joints, strength, and general
athleticism.
That's the real secret to eye-catching hops in spring-loaded feet.
This is how I turn my feet into walking trampolines.